Mister,
thank you for saving me.
Yeah.
By the way, mister,
I saw a huge, terrifying eye
deep in the cold pool.
Could there be an evil spirit
in this cold pool?
There is nothing in the water.
You were frightened,
so you saw it wrong.
Go back and rest.
Impossible.
I definitely didn't see it wrong.
I really...
Go back and rest now.
Oh, okay.
Fine.
Sigh.
Are you punishing me?
What did I do wrong?
This bell...
The demonic cult is invading!
He said he wanted me
to supervise Bai's writing,
but he actually wanted Bai to spy on me.
Bai,
let's go out for a walk.
The old monster asked me
to read and write.
I don't dare to slack off.
Oh.
Everyone knows the Yan Sect is powerful.
Why would the demonic cult come to die?
Do they want something?
If there is something they want
from the Yan Sect,
it should
be this.
It's empty.
No wonder it's so quiet.
The demonic cult is invading outside,
but they are sleeping soundly.
Looks like it's time
to consider making fish soup.
Red beans grow in the southern land,
how many branches sprout in spring?
I hope you gather more,
for this thing represents
lovesickness the most.
This poem...
lovesickness.
Who is she missing?
Sister.
I definitely didn't
see it wrong yesterday.
There must be something wrong
with the cold pool.
I have to go again
and figure it out.
You still want to follow me?
I shook you off.
Wow, there's actually a hot spring here,
and it smells like flowers.
Madam thinks she shook us off.
What should we do next?
The sect leader has ordered
that we cannot trespass here.
Let's just wait here.
It must be very comfortable
to take a bath here.
Are you...
going to take a bath with me?
See no
evil!
Did no one tell you
that you are not allowed to enter here?
No,
what am I expecting?